Zyre Iverzon S. Mendoza

() +63 949 809 1320

https://zyre-mendoza.github.io/portfolio/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

As a Computer Science graduate with 1 year of professional experience in web development and programming, I am proficient in HTML, CSS, PHP, and JavaScript. My enthusiasm for UI/UX design drives me to create intuitive and engaging digital experiences. Eager to continuously learn and adapt, I am dedicated to bringing creative ideas and effective solutions to every project.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

National Economic and Development Authority

October 2024 - Current

Information Systems Analyst I

Analyzing NEDA's internal services' needs for digitalization and automation, and developing a web application using Laravel to address these needs.

Salenga Law Firm July 2023 - July 2024

Programmer

Started developing a Salary App with a decentralized database. We also created their websites.

Technologies used: Rust, Dioxus, Axum, SLED DB, Nostr, Bitcoin Core, NGINX, CloudFlare, Wordpress, Ngrok, Tailwind.

Digital King Inc.

September 2023 - December 2023

Web Developer - Freelance

Created and maintained their clients' websites. Also helped in SEO practices. created SEO-boosting pages.

PhilNITS Corporation

February 2023 - May 2023

Intern

Collected geospatial data and integrated it into GIS systems to create more accurate maps and to analyze spatial relationships. Displaying map results to the web using Laravel and Leaflet.

SKILLS

- PHP: Laravel
- CSS: Bootstrap, Sass, Tailwind CSS
- Javascript: React JS, jQuery, GSAP
- Rust: Axum, Dioxus, Nostr SDK
- Wordpress: Elementor, Basic SEO
- **Design**: Figma, Canva
- Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, SLED DB
- Data Analytics Tool: QGIS

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Science in Computer Science

Don Bosco Technical College

Jun 2019 - Jun 2023

• Cum Laude

THESIS

"Geographic Information System (GIS) Assisted Assessment of Flood Hazard Areas and Improvement of Provincial Disaster Risk Reduction and Management Office (PDRRMO) Of the Municipality of Lingayen, Province of Pangasinan."

 Our aim is to support the PDRRMO by analyzing accurate flood hazard data, implementing mitigation measures, and improving the NDRRMP. GIS technology helps assess and map flood-prone areas, enhancing flood risk management and disaster preparedness.